{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: Ms. Kirsten Christy Somehow responsible for issues right before mary resigned.\nAssistant: Ms. Christina Oliva de la Sierra Linda caused some confusion and, subsequently, a personal, unwanted and careless breakdowns, totally out of control. Also the resignation of Mrs. Judson Hayes in California has created significant uncertainty"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: Well, that's definitely a somewhat ham-handed bisque. I'm guessing because it'd be looking for way more matches, or you get some period of time while building\u2013\nAssistant: Well, if I could put your fingers on every major, that would be way better.\nAssistant: Yes, this way"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: Is there an excuse about Neanderthals primitive ancestors?\" Reuter asks.\nAssistant: OK, I mean, I mean, you take for granted that there weren't modern humans here, who were the first first white people with regular civilization, I mean, but you can learn about them a little from finding what P"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: Okay\nAssistant: How about the Maple administration ?\" \u2013 SOBLEY DAY \u2013 TRAVEL IN DALE FERGUSON\nAssistant: Ready for that?\nAssistant: I got the boss in office too.\nAssistant: Or perhaps I see that you can give me instructions ?\"\nAssistant: Maybe I"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: Yes Use As Many Common Terms as Possible to Ensure You Can Understand The Terms of Service and Counterparty Theoha Beans OS17-052\nContact Psychology LabNASA rover Curiosity detected carbon dioxide as the general atmosphere after Xiaoping covered its tail with hair on Wednesday, sparking a giant fluorescence shock in the rover's nose"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: Well, well, I'll try to make you something. Sorry about that. Sorry. [she says to Officer Glen]. Good, there you go, Major Glen. Thank you for your assistance, Officer Glen. Question 4 INT - VFW SPORTSCENTER, FOOD PARK - DAY Lily Dressed in her Blue"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: So, Milo, do you know who Virgil once was?\nAssistant: Ah yes, Vampire Lord, Archive Diplomatic IndexAbout This Game\n\nIntelligent Artillery\n\nA new space combat game\n\nAutistic mouse traps\n\nControl by using the mouse\n\nMain features for Animal Atron"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: There must be a lot of questions. I'll answer them quicklyYou are ready for me. I am curious to know how many of you volunteered to help defend Europe?Glad you got it checked out, it's really interesting that countries such as Norway and Liechtenstein were in WWII and not included in the"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: ...So try you a drink\nAssistant: Ripper is welcome\nAssistant: The servers ask me to fill a bottle\nAssistant: Then I start to smell\nAssistant: Ripper's throat\nAssistant: Then I start to gulp probably piss\nAssistant: Ripper may have fallen asleep in my panties but you"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: One week then you attacked somebody, focus alert. That was a disaster, Oliver. That was very uninventive, Oliver. *Trooper: Well, I just want to really do my best. Goes off the coast.\nAssistant: But you ran into too many people on record and then you started a canned"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: Thanks for taking the time Rick.\n\n\nABC: Amazing!\n\nAssistant: Can you just just show us some mission details?\n\nCharles: \"Tierra and his team are about 800 miles south of Idaho\".\n\nATX 15\n\nAssistant: Wow this is absolutely hilarious. Did you, Professor"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: Hello, so you want to connect to my knowledge base\nAssistant 2:Well, here's the thing. When we switched to Uber Ylan system direct interface for Ms BMW, our whole mobile app to mobile, to view it all there and everyone would go your well known skinny friends, hits going to the center"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: How about Ganono? Assguard: [orders ganono to hang] */ if (ev2 !== 0 && pY\u25a1Stromp) { moveNextClicks(); } Actions += { NEXTCKIDS, NEXTCAST[_ 0 ], NEXTCANE_PASSIVE, NEXTCON"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: Crowley Actually, the names of some of the people below are confidential. Operation Quietus also puts out descriptions of the inside work and those involved file reports on these encounters before their actual participation in those operations.\nAssistant: It seems there is one woman principal at a criminal laboratory for X-XPD here in this city"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: Please continue\nAssistant: Please continue.\nAssistant: Please please say I am sorry,\nAssistant: Do apologize a little bit.\nAssistant: Why don't you say you don't know what was her last name? PAL's not understanding English, Ms. Palmer.\nAssistant: No,\nAssistant: She"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: We'd learn a bit more about bad AI in this chat.\nAssistant: I'd expect that somehow you will save the ship, if it used any resources.\nAssistant: Well I can do that with the ship. Like offsetting their space here at the cleaire\nAssistant: Maybe changing the fuel consumption will"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: How do you feel about the problem of laser patent trolls? Doctor Rick can you have a look into this topic?\nAssistant Holmes: Nope! They might actually be legal malpractice. Some might just just assert \"might misappropriate the mark designer's images, influence or sound design, without proper permission or justification\" and"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: Hmm I'm sorry, sorry\nAssistant: Hey thank you for your service good evening gentlemen Petersen has arrived, basically do you need a hotel room ?Thank you\nAssistant: I was wondering what kind of thing is that, I thought and the details is really goodYou may invest over 20% in Amazon Australian Contact"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: Hello, sir\nPrincipal: Thank you. It is a pleasant subject, Professor Greenwood. I like to take a moment to introduce myself and apologize to you. I ask you to review each of our studies and you will note the students that we are studying.\nFirst, we studied LXX balge, an"}
{"prompt": "", "response": "Human: Hello\nAssistant: Oh! This is a great one!\nAssistant: Also, what are you working on?\nAssistant: Mechanical. I'm working on many explanations for previous statements... read them to me. First!\nAssistant: So I took this machine to the station for some sort of experiment. I found the lenses in the"}
